<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-12-10T09:26:12+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">garfbradaz.github.io</title><subtitle>My Github page</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Arise New Blog</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/2018/07/07/Arise-New-Blog.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Arise New Blog" /><published>2018-07-07T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2018-07-07T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/2018/07/07/Arise-New-Blog</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/2018/07/07/Arise-New-Blog.html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;its-alive&quot;&gt;It’s alive!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have wanted to move &lt;a href=&quot;https://mywebanecdotes.com/&quot;&gt;my current&lt;/a&gt; off Wordpress for sometime, but time has always been a factor. As a developer I find myself living within &lt;em&gt;Visual Studio Code&lt;/em&gt;, so I decided to set up a blog which can:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Use my Visual Studio Code&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Use my git skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I knew github has &lt;a href=&quot;https://pages.github.com/&quot;&gt;Github Pages&lt;/a&gt;, and it used &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt;. So I have started a Github page. So this is day one. I chose a minimal theme  for the site, and each change to the site I will document as a blog post. Think of them as Release Notes!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I move on I change the style and layout etc, but for now (and posterity) here is the Home Page from day 1:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/posts/day_1.PNG&quot; alt=&quot;Day 1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>gareth</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="misc" /><category term="jekyll" /><summary type="html">It’s alive! I have wanted to move my current off Wordpress for sometime, but time has always been a factor. As a developer I find myself living within Visual Studio Code, so I decided to set up a blog which can: Use my Visual Studio Code Use my git skills I knew github has Github Pages, and it used Jekyll. So I have started a Github page. So this is day one. I chose a minimal theme for the site, and each change to the site I will document as a blog post. Think of them as Release Notes! As I move on I change the style and layout etc, but for now (and posterity) here is the Home Page from day 1:</summary></entry></feed>